Justin Ng

Outreach Associate - Big Reuse

Brooklyn, NY 11204 ng.justin07@gmail.com (347) 241-1361

I am an Environmental advocate who has a passion in working within waste management. I studied at Hunter College and graduated with a Bachelors in Environmental Studies. In my previous role we worked closely with the NYC Department of Sanitation as part of their outreach team for the organics curbside collections program. Waste management is an integral part of keeping a city clean, functioning, and is a big part in keeping our environment sustainable for the future.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Outreach Associate

Big Reuse - Brooklyn, NY September 2017 to April 2020

- Hiring and Screening Potential Candidates
- Engaging with community organizations
- · Acting as a liaison for troubleshooting problems with organics collections in apartment buildings
- Community Education and Presentations
- Scheduling and planning
- Excel and data management

Intern

Department of Sanitation - Manhattan, NY June 2016 to August 2016

Educate residents and homeowners about organic recycling

- Worked with Interns/NYC Service members during door to door canvassing
- Working with partner organizations to help educate residents on composting
- Worked on Excel spreadsheets to compile address lists and schedules

Intern

Tactical Anglers - Brooklyn, NY January 2015 to July 2015

Packaged thousands of fishing supplies

- Delivered packages to be shipped
- Tested products

Education

B.A. Environmental Studies in Management and Policy

Hunter College - New York, NY

Skills

- educating (Less than 1 year)
- Highly organized (Less than 1 year)
- Microsoft Office (Less than 1 year)
- MS OFFICE (Less than 1 year)
- teaching (Less than 1 year)
- Presentation Skills
- Outside Sales
- Sales
- · Cold Calling
- Door-to-Door Experience
- CSS
- JavaScript
- HTML5
- Door-to-Door Experience
- · Presentation Skills

Additional Information

Skills:

- 1. Working coding knowledge of HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- 2. Public speaking and presentation experience
- 3. Maintaining clientele relationships
- 4. Proficient in Microsoft Office tools
- 5. Canvassing Experience
- 6. Great interpersonal and communication skills
- 7. Driver's license
- 8. Highly organized
- 9. Proven to be able to create, maintain, and manage schedules
- 10. Ability to work in a team environment
- 11. Highly capable working independently
- 12. Can work under pressure
- 13. Experience in teaching and educating others
- 14. Exemplary skills in handling customers